# CONTACT

- Minsk, Belarus
- +375 44 776 62 14
- vladimirlyn@gmail.com
- in in/vladimirliankevich
- github.com/MillionerMIN
- t.me/vladimir\_lian
- portfolio

# SKILLS

- React / Redux / Thunk
- JavaScript / TypeScript
- Axios / Rest API
- Material-UI / Bootstrap 5
- HTML 5 / CSS 3 / SASS
- Git

## EDUCATION

2021

#### Fron-end Developer

(React/ Redux/ TypeScript)
IT-Incubator

2019-2023 (extramural)

## **Civil Engineering**

Belarusian National Technical University

2003-2007

#### **Civil Engineering**

branch BNTU «Minsk State College of Architecture and Civil Engineering»

## PERSONAL PROFILE

Front-end developer with experience in creating landing pages, SPA with React / Redux (JS / TS). Confident understanding of react-redux architecture. Internship on projects. In my free time, I solve problems on Codewars. I also plan to raise my level of English to Intermediate, also plan study NodeJS, MySQL.

In the future, I see myself as a Full Stack Developer. Open to your suggestions.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Front-end Developer, Freelance

MAY 2021 - PRESENT

- React development using redux, react-redux, react-router-dom, redux-thunk, axios, formik, ant-design libraries
- Work with Hooks, TypeScript
- Reusable components development
- experience in cross-browser, adaptive, responsive development, CSS-preprocessors. Implemented flowauthorization, notification, forms (Formik and Redux-form)

# **Work Manager** (foreman), UM-70 OJSC Trest 15 Spetsstroy FEB 2012 - AUG 2021

- Organization of construction production
- Communication and reporting to the customer
- Quality control and timing of work
- Paperwork for putting objects into operation

# Work Manager (foreman), OJSC Stroymaztrest

AUG 2007 - JAN 2012

- Distribution of production tasks
- Distribution of wages among employees
- Communication with the customer

#### LANGUAGES

English: pre-intermediate (in progress)

